ILGWU. Gus Tyler papers, 5780/096
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III. Speeches
  - Speeches. October, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Speeches. November, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Speeches. December, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Speeches. January, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Speeches. February, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Speeches. March, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - Speeches. April, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - Speeches. May, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - Speeches. June, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - Speeches. July, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - Speeches. August, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - Speeches. September, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - Speeches. October, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - Speeches. November, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - Speeches. December, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 57)
  - Speeches. January, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 58)
  - Speeches. February, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 59)
  - Speeches. March, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 60)
  - Speeches. April, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 61)
  - Speeches. May, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 62)
  - Speeches. June, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 63)
  - Speeches. July, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 64)
  - Speeches. August, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 65)
  - Speeches. September, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 66)
  - Speeches. October, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 67)
  - Speeches. November, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 68)
  - Speeches. December, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 69)
  - Speeches. January, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 70)
  - Speeches. February, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 71)
  - Speeches. March, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 72)
  - Speeches. July, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 73)
  - Speeches. September, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 74)
  - Speeches. October, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 75)
  - Speeches. November, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 76)
  - Speeches. December, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 77)
  - Speeches. January, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 78)
  - Updated Speeches. Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 2] (Box 30, Folder 79)
  - Updated Speeches. Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 2] (Box 30, Folder 80)
- Series IV. Miscellaneous
  - Article. "Affirmative Gerrymandering", 1977 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Business International Corporation. Correspondence., 1976 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Article. "Jimmy Carter", 1977-1980 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous. Ideas of… [folder 1 of 6] (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous. Ideas of… [folder 2 of 6] (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous. Ideas of… [folder 3 of 6] (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous. Ideas of… [folder 4 of 6] (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous. Ideas of… [folder 5 of 6] (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous. Ideas of… [folder 6 of 6] (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous. Mayor John V. Lindsay, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous. Present Tense Symposium, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous, 1964-1969 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Magic Circle Book Shop [folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Magic Circle Book Shop [folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - ILGWU Publications, 1965-1995 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - ILGWU Publications, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - ILGWU Publications, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - ILGWU Chorus (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Music Sheets. "The Dream Goes On" (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Music Sheets. "Pins and Needles" (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Script. "Pins and Needles" [folder 1 of 3] (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Script. "Pins and Needles" [folder 2 of 3] (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Script. "Pins and Needles" [folder 3 of 3] (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Tyler, Gus. Miscellaneous (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Academy of Political Science. Certificate to Gus Tyler, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Wang Professional Computer Word Processing Student Guide (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Friends of the Department of Labor, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Lectures and WEVD Recordings (Box 32, Folder 18)